

# **Guilherme Morone Araujo**

**Date of birth:** 10/02/2001 | **Nationality:** Brazilian | **Gender:** Male | **Email address:** 

guimorone@gmail.com | Website: https://guimorone.github.io | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/guimorone

#### ABOUT ME

Originally from Rio but now based in Recife, I've had the privilege of growing up in two vibrant cities. My passions are as diverse as my background, ranging from an avid love for games and books to an insatiable curiosity for travel and technology. Furthermore, I am always eager to explore new opportunities and challenges that can help me grow both as a professional and as a person, fueled by my passion for learning and applying new technologies to solve real-world problems.

I have been working on Software Development since 2022. Not only that, but I am used to developing Big Data applications that demand high efficiency, scalability, and low cost. All my projects demanded skills in web development, data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud computing, in order to deliver quality solutions to clients.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

10/04/2024 - CURRENT Recife, Brazil

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER NEUROTECH** 

#### Full-time job:

- In general, using skills in software and backend development with Python, FastAPI, Terraform, Git, Airflow, Bash and cloud computing on AWS.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- Ensure high-quality, scalable application development.
- Using Amazon Web Services such as Lambda, DynamoDB, EC2, Athena, S3 and more.

Department Hydra - Neurolake | Email guilherme.morone@neurotech.com.br | Website https://www.neurotech.com.br

10/04/2024 - 31/05/2024 Recife, Brazil

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER |ALAN**

#### Full-time job:

• Worked as a Full Stack developer using Vue.js and Quasar along with Python and Lambda Functions (AWS).

Website https://jalan.com.br

01/03/2024 - 31/03/2024 Recife, Brazil

**MOBILE ENGINEER** ACA.SO

#### Freelancer:

Worked as a Mobile Engineer in a project (aca.so mobile app) using React Native.

Website https://aca.so

01/07/2023 - 28/12/2023 Recife, Brazil

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

#### Freelancer:

- Website made with 3 more colleagues to an external customer.
- The main purpose is to identify bank check fields easily, so you do not have to type manually.
- The bank check OCR is based on our customer's API, we did not implement it, just the website.
- It also offers API Integration, history download and other features.
- Developed using React, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS and Django (Python).

01/02/2022 - 28/12/2023 Recife, Brazil

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER ONCASE**

#### Full-time job:

- Developed Big Data applications with a focus on high efficiency, scalability, and low cost.
- Developed frontend applications using React (JavaScript, TypeScript and HTML/CSS) and Redux.
- Implemented backend functionality using Python frameworks Flask and Django.
- Implemented effective CI/CD pipelines for seamless integration and deployment through Docker and GitHub Actions.
- In general, utilized skills in web development (Django, React and HTML/CSS), data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud computing.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.

- Enhanced customer relationships through the delivery of top-notch solutions.
- Ensured high-quality and scalable application development.
- Hosted applications on Google Cloud Platform using Cloud Run and Artifact Registry.
- Utilized Amazon Web Services for hosting, leveraging services like Amplify, Route53, and Lambda.

Website https://www.oncase.com.br

01/08/2022 - 31/10/2022 Recife, Brazil

**MOBILE ENGINEER INSPACE** 

#### Freelancer:

• Identification of objects (censored specificity) from a mobile camera for legal purposes.

Website https://inspace.tech

01/06/2021 - 31/10/2021 Recife, Brazil

**GAME DEVELOPER EDUCANDUS** 

## Internship:

• I have worked as a game developer using Construct 3 software and JavaScript, building educational games for students from preschool to high school levels.

Website https://educandus.com.br

01/05/2020 - 30/12/2020 Recife, Brazil

**GAME DEVELOPER EDUCANDUS** 

## Internship:

• I have worked as a game developer using Construct 3 software and JavaScript, building educational games for students from preschool to high school levels.

Website https://educandus.com.br

### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/02/2019 - 31/08/2024 Recife, Brazil

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING Federal University of Pernambuco (UFPE)

Website <a href="https://portal.cin.ufpe.br">https://portal.cin.ufpe.br</a>

**Field of study** Software and applications development and analysis, Computer use, Database and network design and administration, Information and communication technologies not elsewhere classified, Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs) not further defined, Electronics and automation

Final grade 9.01/10.0 | Level in EQF EQF level 6

01/06/2022 - 31/03/2024

STUDENT TEACHING ASSISTANT Federal University of Pernambuco (UFPE)

- Dedicated Student Teaching Assistant in the field of Software and Systems Engineering.
- Provided invaluable support to students in software development and requirements engineering, with a primary goal of crafting top-tier applications of exceptional quality.

Website https://portal.cin.ufpe.br | Field of study Software and applications development and analysis

15/03/2024 - 03/04/2024

THE COMPLETE FLUTTER DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP WITH DART Udemy

Website https://udemy.com

Link https://ude.my/UC-3fd9599a-bff2-4960-8d34-dbb3b41ced55

01/03/2023 - 14/03/2023

GOOGLE CLOUD COMPUTING FOUNDATIONS: DATA, ML, AND AI IN GOOGLE CLOUD - LOCALES Google Cloud Skills Boost

Website https://www.cloudskillsboost.google

Link <a href="https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?">https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?</a>
<a href="https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?">https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?</a>
<a href="https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?">https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?</a>
<a href="https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?">https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?</a>
<a href="https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?">https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3311200?</a>

### GOOGLE CLOUD COMPUTING FOUNDATIONS: INFRASTRUCTURE IN GOOGLE CLOUD - LOCALES Google Cloud Skills Boost

Website https://www.cloudskillsboost.google

Link https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3303084

01/03/2023 - 13/03/2023

**GOOGLE CLOUD COMPUTING FOUNDATIONS: NETWORKING** Google Cloud Skills Boost

Website https://www.cloudskillsboost.google

Link https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3305980

01/03/2023 - 12/03/2023

GOOGLE CLOUD COMPUTING FOUNDATIONS: CLOUD COMPUTING FUNDAMENTALS - LOCALES Google Cloud Skills Boost

Website https://www.cloudskillsboost.google

Link https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public\_profiles/d8f54101-4f80-4aee-8e46-2320e3e20646/badges/3302433

01/04/2020 - 21/04/2020

THE COMPLETE 2020 WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP Udemy

Website https://udemy.com

Link https://ude.my/UC-5d594204-a414-4cb1-a388-72e3daf7c1c6

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PORTUGUESE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEA	WRITING	
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C2	C1	C1	C2
GERMAN	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

## **Digital Skills - Test Results**

lnformation and data literacy	ADVANCED	Level 6 / 6
B Communication and collaboration	ADVANCED	Level 6 / 6
© Digital content creation	ADVANCED	Level 6 / 6
Safety     ■ Safety	ADVANCED	Level 6 / 6
Problem solving	ADVANCED	Level 6 / 6

Results from <u>self-assessment</u> based on <u>The Digital Competence Framework 2.1</u>

Games			
Reading Books			
Travelling			
Gym			
Movies			